//our question database
let STORE = [{
  question: 'What is the state capitol of Maine?',
  answers: ['Bangor','Portland','Augusta','StockBridge'],
  correctAnswer: 'Augusta'
},
{
  question: 'What is the state capitol of Michigan?',
  answers: ['Lansing','Detroit','SouthField','Royal Oak'],
  correctAnswer: 'Lansing'
},
{
  question: 'What is the state capitol of Florida?',
  answers: ['Talahasee','Saint PetersBerg','Miami','ClearWater'],
  correctAnswer: 'Talahasee'
},
{
  question: 'What is the state capitol of California?',
  answers: ['Los Angeles','San Fransisco','San Diego', 'Sacremento'],
  correctAnswer: 'Sacremento'
},
{
  question: 'What is the capitol of Washington?',
  answers: ['Seattle','Olympia','Tacoma','Spokane'],
  correctAnswer: 'Tacoma'
},
{
  question: 'What is the state capitlol of Oregon?',
  answers: ['Portland', 'Eugene', 'Bend', 'Salem'],
  correctAnswer: 'Salem'
},
{
  question: 'What is the state capitol of Montana?',
  answers: ['Bozeman','Helena','Billings','Great Falls'],
  correctAnswer: 'Helena'
},
{
  question: 'What is the state capitol of Texas?',
  answers: ['Austin','Dallas','Fort Worth', 'El Paso'],
  correctAnswer: 'Austin'
},
{
  question: 'What is the state capitol of Idaho?',
  answers: ['Idaho Falls','Boise','Twin Falls', 'Nampa'],
  correctAnswer: 'Boise'
},
{
  question: 'What is the state capitol of Kentucky',
  answers: ['Frankfort','Louisville','Lexington','Bardstown'],
  correctAnswer: 'Frankfort'
}
];
